Good day to you.
What do you want?
Boy, Get in here now!
What took you so long?
I was cleaning the fan switches.
Watch the store.
I've got some selling to do.
Outlanders. They think we know nothing.
They seemed nice to me.
Clean the racks...
...then you can go home.
Are you going to pay for that?
It costs seven wupiupi.
Is this yours?
Careful, Sebulba.
He's a big time outlander.
I'd hate to see you diced
before we race again.
Next time we race, boy,
it will be the end of you.
If you weren't a slave
I'd squash you now.
Yeah, it'd be a pity if
you had to pay for me.
Your friend is a foolish one, methinks.
You're such a joker, Ani.
Better stop your friend's betting
or I'll end up owning him too.
You won't walk away from this one...
...you slave scum.
Don't count on it, slime ball.
You're bantha fodder!
Welcome.
Begin the race!